(Happiness Doesn't Come Easy)
- Nice to see you all. - Nice to see you.
- All right. - Nice to see you.
It's MINHO whom I beat in the race.
(During the 100m running race on the field day, )
(Hyun Moo took the lead thanks to the false start.)
(That's how he managed to get a sly victory.)
You really posted that on your social media.
- How could you really post that? - You're something else.
- He really posted that. - I did it when the show was airing.
- He's something else. - I wanted to get you all worked up.
- Gosh, seriously. - He's something.
It's like a badge of honor.
I'll say that everywhere I go.
- I'll play that video to everyone. - Gosh.
As for the man of the clips we're about to watch,
he is the only person who defeated MINHO.
- He's talking about himself. - It's Moomoo.
He's the new icon of running.
- Let's watch my clips. - He just killed the running trend.
- He killed it. - It was popular for a long time.
I guess the trend is over now.
He's stealing that as soon as Kian84 goes away.
(I Love Myself)
(Decked out in a flashy outfit, Moomoo hits the street.)
- Don't I look like I'm in RIIZE? - RIIZE?
More like rice.
- Brown rice. - The yellow one, right?
- Rice. - The yellow one.
I must be brown rice since it's yellow.
(He heads somewhere while exuding the air of brown rice.)
(Observing intently)
Is that the place?
(Surprised)
Where are you going?
(Curious)
(Let me see.)
What?
"Requiring assistance on weekdays."
"Assistance to look around..."
You have to wait your turn for assistance?
You must be there as soon as it opens.
- Really? - It's in Seongsu-dong.
This is crazy.
You're wearing a matching outfit to the color of the store.
Exactly.
Do you wear a red outfit to go to McDonald's?
Of course. I even dress up as a clown when I go there.
A clown outfit?
- Just to have a burger. - To have McMorning.
You have to pretend to be a clown in the morning.
(This kind of commitment is required to be a fashionista.)
- Do you go to KFC as a grandpa? - You can just go as you are.
I have to dye my hair like him to go to KFC.
(Must I spell it out for you?)
(He hovers around the yellow shop in his yellow outfit.)
Look at this punk.
- Look at this punk. - It's a puppy.
- How cute. - Is that a real puppy?
(Moomoo's friend is fast asleep.)
- Really? - It's a puppy.
My gosh.
- You two have a matching outfit. - How cute.
(Laughing)
(Our matching outfits are cute.)
- Are you Customer Number Three? - Yes, that's me.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Let me help you inside. - Okay.
Come on in.
(He finally enters the mysterious place.)
(It's the go-to spot for all things running.)
- I didn't know about this store. - For running.
They sell all kinds of running gear in this store.
(Colorful running shoes of different types are on display.)
(Interested)
(It's full of trendy running gear.)
(The Rainbow Club members enjoy running.)
- Mr. Monkey! - Mr. Monkey!
(Even Mr. Monkey is a powerful runner.)
Let's go, Mr. Monkey.
(Thank you.)
You've been waiting for a very long time.
At last,
I, Moomoo, will join the running trend.
This running trend...
From now on, people will associate running with me, not Kian84.
Starting today, I'm Moorathoner.
(Let's go!)
(What is this?)
Moorathoner? Seriously?
(The shocking and terrifying nickname, Moorathoner)
- From now on... - Look at my face.
- It's brimming with determination. - Look at his pursed lips.
He's so annoying to look at.
If Sean quits running after seeing this, it'd be crazy.
- It'd be crazy. - If Sean quits,
- it proves how influential I am. - Right.
I've been very tired lately because of my demanding workload.
A lot of my friends told me that running is the best way...
- It sure is. - to boost my energy.
When I went to Na Rae's grandmother's place.
I was quite amazed by Kian84.
- Seriously. He was amazing. - He had great stamina.
He had great stamina.
Running might have damaged his looks.
But his stamina has improved.
I'd say Kian84's running style is demanding on the body.
But my running is all about wellness.
- Wellness? - I'm cherishing my body.
It's called I-Love-Myself Running.
- What's running for wellness? - I love myself.
"Run as you love yourself."
It's about wellness. If it's too hard, take a break.
Don't be stressed. Don't curse.
If it's too hard, just stop.
That's a good motto.
Just stop. Sit down. Lie down.
Because we only see hardcore runners like Kian84,
as for people like me who don't know much about running,
we can't even dare to run. We're too scared to try it.
- Look. KEY isn't doing it. - Me?
"That's not my thing."
But that's not true, KEY.
Even KEY can do it.
If I can do this, he can too.
It helps me improve my endurance without burdening my body.
I call it the Moomoo Running.
I'll lead a new kind of running trend.
- It does sound convincing. - Right?
Yes.
(Skeptical)
Then what's your target distance?
But you need to run at least 10km or more...
to get your money's worth out of your running gear.
- That's too much. About 8km? - What?
- Yes. - That was a huge decision for you.
- It was a huge decision. - That won't be easy.
- It's a full course marathon to me. - Of course.
- Right. - To first timers, it could be.
- That's a long distance. - Of course.
So what brings you to our store today?
The longest distance I've run in my life is 3km.
- What? - I've done it only once.
I almost died when I did that.
I'm a complete newbie.
- I know nothing about running. - Okay.
I need good gear to make up for my lack of skills.
- I see. That's important. - Yes.
- I need to optimize my gear. - We have to start with good gear.
- That's the first thing we need. - Yes.
Could you show me some items?
- For a newbie who has no gear. - I see.
- Then let's start with shoes... - Yes.
- and cover the rest one at a time. - Yes, please.
(Clearing his throat)
Do you have trendy shoes?
- Trendy shoes? - From a brand that's on the rise.
- Well, trendy shoes... - You're at a running gear shop.
How about shoes that play music?
Those shoes these days can even light up.
- The front part lights up. - Some shoes play music.
- They even light up. - Do you mean those light-up shoes?
- You'll never get into an accident. - Exactly.
- They are so trendy. - They sound pretty good.
- They are trendy among kids. - On rainy days.
(Kid Moomoo is looking for music-less trendy shoes.)
- Trendy shoes? - From a brand that's on the rise.
Do you... Oh, I see.
I can recommend you exactly what you're looking for.
The first pair I'm going to show you...
- has a strong customer base. - That's it.
- You like hearing that. - That's it.
I don't want a pair everyone wears. You know?
- Only real runners... - "He knows what's up."
- That's it. - "He knows what's up."
(He knows what's up.)
(Jumping)
- What are you doing? - These shoes have a solid feel.
They do.
If I run 3km in these,
I'll pass out.
- Are they from the new season? - Yes.
They were launched for the first time last year.
The colors have been changing.
Newer editions keep coming out.
The most important thing to look for when picking out shoes is...
how they feel on your feet.
- It's how they feel on your feet. - What is he doing?
- Okay. - The upper...
You have especially big and wide feet.
- He's so distracting. - So...
- make sure they aren't too narrow. - They aren't.
- There must be this much room here. - They're so comfortable.
So these shoes are trendy now, right?
(Reconfirming)
I like how they feel on my feet and the level of bounciness.
They're good shoes.
What do you think?
- I'll get these. - Those?
- I'll ring them up for you. - Yes, please.
I want a breathable outfit.
Is there an outfit that wipes sweat naturally?
An outfit that wipes sweat naturally?
I wore an outfit from this brand when I recently ran 100km.
(Listening intently)
Does it absorb sweat well?
Would you say it's the best?
- Personally, I'd say it's the best. - Really?
I wore this top with these shorts.
This was my outfit.
Do I need to get them dry cleaned?
I recommend washing them by hand.
- My mom is good at that. - I think...
(Joking)
My mom is good at that.
- He's the icon of unfilial sons. - I'm serious. She likes doing that.
Seriously.
- She really likes doing that. - Come on. Don't do that.
She takes out the laundry in the washer...
and washes them by hand.
- She takes them out on purpose. - You know what I think?
You need to serve in the military again.
He should.
- He must join the Marines camp. - You need to cry about your mom.
- Should I hold the camp for you? - Yes.
- Join the camp. - Right.
Say that after beating me in a running race.
(Feeling dizzy)
Shirts with this kind of fabric dry up sweat faster.
But you can wear this too. It's not a huge difference.
Could you also pay attention...
- to the style? - Sure.
I'll bring them, so you can try them on.
I want to see what kind of outfit he'll wear.
This is a disaster.
(He hesitantly comes out in his first outfit.)
(Everything under his shirt is visible.)
Hold on. Maybe, that's not so bad. Here's why.
You'll cross the finish line first.
This is how I beat MINHO.
They would hit the finish line first.
- You're blessed with your body. - You bet.
Your body type was made for running.
(Unsightly)
(His body type can be quite aggressive.)
He should change into another outfit.
My goodness. Oh, no.
- I'm sorry. - I can never wear this.
(He quickly changes into the second outfit and comes out.)
- This one... - They feel so light, right?
- This outfit looks good. - That's much better.
- It's a great outfit. - The outfit looks great on you.
That's better.
Gosh, I love it.
It feels like I'm wearing the dry sauna outfit.
- It felt like I had nothing on. - It did, right?
- Great. - They felt so airy.
(His movements are lighter.)
- If you like them... - I love them.
Great. It's like I have nothing on. I love them.
Socks too?
Then socks... If that's the case...
You'll buy socks too?
Those are functional socks.
This wraps around your body nicely.
Wait. It looks like a vest puppies wear.
What? Runners actually wear that?
From this angle...
There's more stuff to buy?
He's getting his knees taped just to run 8km?
But novice runners should get them.
- Of course. - Yes.
- That was the right thing to do. - It's already hurting my leg hair.
- So... - I already know it'll be painful...
to remove the tapes.
You can run 42km with this gear.
Then I'll go and run.
- Let me go over the items now. - Okay.
- So everything comes out... - Yes.
- to 1,002.2 dollars. - What? You spent 1,000 dollars?
If you sign up to our membership, we give a ten-percent discount.
Really? Then I should.
- I must get the discount. - Sign up.
- You must sign up. - It's a big discount. So you must.
- That's 100 dollars off. - He can save 100 dollars.
With the discount, it's 901.98 dollars.
- I'll proceed with this bill. - Okay.
Could you sign here?
(The man with old money makes sure to get the discount.)
When you bought them and put them on,
- Yes? - it felt good, right?
- It felt great. - That's all that matters.
- That's good then. - He felt good. That's all.
- He was spending his own money. - Exactly.
You should participate in a competition too.
Let's go.
(Fully dressed with new and trendy items)
He bought everything from head to toe.
My gosh. Come on.
(He feels good, but for some reason, he seems a bit drawn.)
I hate it.
It looks like you're headed to a waterpark.
(Moomoo is visiting a waterpark.)
- He's heading to the wave pool. - Or to the water sports spot.
It looks like you're going wakeboarding.
His outfit is misleading. Seriously.
You see people dressed like that in Cheongpyeong.
So many people there wear...
- outfits in that color. - Right.
- People with the dialect. - Why doesn't it look good on me?
When I tell people I started running...
and they recognize the brand I'm wearing,
it will boost my energy.
"I see. You know what's up."
I'm pushing it with the brand.
I need some kind of momentum like that.
That's why I don't understand people who run alone at 5am alone.
I must run during the morning commute.
I'll run along the Gangbyeon Expressway...
during the morning commute.
(Everyone will take pictures of me.)
People have to watch me.
Who takes pictures of you like that?
"He takes good care of himself."
- "Look at his shoes." - Exactly.
- "He's wearing that brand." - Exactly.
When people are taking pictures, I'll drink water.
(Sipping)
(Oh, dear...)
They'll capture that moment.
It will go on social media and viral.
- He has such an ambitious dream. - Viral, my foot.
Then I would be leading the running trend.
I'd take over then.
That's what I'm aiming for.
(Holding back his laughter)
Since I started,
- Yes. - I must go all the way.
I mean it when I say this. You're so cool.
He's something else.
(The man who will lead the running trend emerges out.)
Great.
Let's go for a run.
- You'll run right away? - I will.
But it's a bit chilly.
It's chilly.
- A taxi? - What?
- You're getting into a taxi! - Hear me out.
- That's not the route I wanted. - What?
I wanted to run a specific route.
- A taxi after shopping like that? - Then you must run there.
- No. - How could you get into a taxi?
I would run over 8km then. That would be too much for me.
- This is like a black comedy show. - This is...
It looks like...
- a satire of modern people. - Right. It does look like that.
This is a straight-up black comedy.
He gets into a taxi after dropping 1,000 dollars.
(He gets into a taxi for his happiness.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you.
All right. Gosh.
- Just a bit. - Yes.
(He quickly goes somewhere.)
(He calls someone as soon as he gets into the taxi.)
- Hello. - Hey.
- Hey. - Who's that?
Where are you?
I'm going somewhere. I'm driving now.
- No way. Is it Sean? - It must be Sean.
- There are days when you don't run. - I ran this morning. At dawn.
You called the ultimate runner.
- I'm going to run 8km. - Okay.
I've never run that long in my life.
- So for the 1st 3km, - Okay.
Run slowly in order to warm up your body.
After running 5km, if it's too much, you can walk.
That's such a useful tip.
I was so grateful when he said it was okay to walk.
Can I eat while running?
Sure, you can.
Just don't eat anything heavy.
- Eat energy bars. - I can't eat sundaeguk, right?
Hold on. If you do that, you're no longer running.
- Your sides could hurt then. - My sides could hurt?
Yes.
- All right. - Okay. Thank you.
Bye.
I'm going to run 8km.
- Se Hyeong runs a lot too. - Today?
I'm a bit scared What if I just start running and...
If you obsess over the act of running,
this awesome sport...
won't be fun for you.
- Ho Young. - You called everyone.
Do you think I can run 8km?
Once I started running, I could finish.
I'm going to run 8km today.
- I'm going to run 8km today. - Why don't you call your mom?
She'll like that.
Did you call every runner you knew?
I did.
I think telling everyone that you will run 8km today is great.
We're almost there.
- Thank you. - Okay.
My gosh.
What about the paper bag?
There are lockers in the subway stations.
- I see. - You'll use the lockers?
I should leave them in the subway station.
I almost got on the subway when I walked down.
What is this?
It takes half a day for you to start running.
That's how it usually is.
That's enough time to finish running 8km.
My gosh, it's cold.
Gosh, was it...
always like this here?
Everyone is wearing a coat.
- Only he's wearing short sleeves. - What?
Look at the couple in the back. "Gosh, he must be out of his mind."
"What's wrong with Hyun Moo?"
- "That poor old man." - Right.
"He has bad knees. He has the pain relief patches on."
Gosh, it's cold.
I'm in the middle of Gwanghwamun.
I'll show you my route at last.
There's a famous route among runners.
There's a puppy run because the route is puppy-shaped.
It's called the puppy run.
Yes. That's a famous one.
It's an easy route.
I watched the YouTube video.
On the smartwatch many runners wear,
the route they run is shown on the map with GPS.
After the run, the route will show up on the map.
Then you'll see that the route is shaped like a puppy.
I'm starting at the jaw of the puppy from Gwanghwamun.
I'll keep running and then go to the Blue House.
After checking out the Blue House,
I'll arrive at Anguk Station and then run up.
After the right turn,
I'll go to Jongno 3-ga Station and head to Jonggak.
(Bosingak)
Then I'll come back to Gwanghwamun.
This puppy run completes a puppy-shaped route.
You're right. My gosh.
- Isn't that cute? - It's cute.
The run includes a tail and a nose.
- That will be a total of 8km? - Yes.
It's called GPS drawing.
A lot of people run to make shapes with their GPS.
Like the sweet potato run in Yeouido and the kangaroo run in Sangam.
- I see. Like the shapes? - Right.
(That's interesting.)
I'm doing the puppy run because...
- I'm a dog lover. - That's true.
I totally agree.
(Everyone knows that Hyun Moo is a dog lover.)
And I look like a Shih Tzu.
I love everything related to dogs.
So I liked the puppy run.
Jongno is one of my favorite spots in Seoul.
There's a plethora of good restaurants.
Not only does it represent our history and traditions,
it also has a lot of trending restaurants.
- It's a mecca of good restaurants. - There are many good restaurants.
My gosh, there are so many old restaurants.
Seosulla-gil.
My gosh, that place.
I still remember the flavor.
It'd feel great to be there.
It's a popular running spot among the zoomers.
There are so many runners in front of Gyeongbokgung.
Since I started to run, I shouldn't stop at 3km or 5km.
I should do a proper challenge.
Running 8km is worthy of being called a challenge.
So I decided to do the puppy run for the first time.
(His 1st challenge to do the 8km puppy run)
My gosh. All right.
(Before the 8km run, he lightly warms up.)
- You look handsome! - You're handsome.
- Hello. - Nice to meet you!
People are watching him.
Hello, I'm a runner. Hey, there.
Students from the countryside came to Seoul on a school trip.
(All right. Let me start running now.)
- You look like Cha Eun Woo! - Cha Eun Woo?
- You think I look like Cha Eun Woo? - Yes!
(A cute gesture for the fans)
(Cheering)
(Feigned laughter)
He really looks like a legit clown.
- He is. - A long time ago in the Joseon Era,
I bet there was a clown in front of the palace.
- Of course. - I'm doing the mask dance there.
I thought I was Hwang Young Cho.
Hwang Young Cho ran over Montjuic.
I will run around Jongno.
That's right.
- I feel dizzy now. - Right.
I'm getting a bit nauseous now.
I'll start running. Bye.
- Good luck! - I got this!
You got this!
(Preparing something)
(Gently)
- What's that? - What is that?
What on earth is that?
I must prevent my facial skin from sagging.
My skin will sag.
That's painful on the ears.
(He finishes putting on the jawline mask.)
Let's go.
Start the GPS.
Three, two, one. Go.
(Starting today, I'm Moorathoner.)
Let's take it slow.
Treat this as slow jogging.
Slowly.
Gosh, it's cold.
(He begins from the front gate of Gwanghwamun...)
(toward Gyeongbokgung Station.)
It's so cold.
That's the same pace as the walker's.
- You just look at it yourself! - Listen.
- He's a fast walker. - What is this?
- Look at that. - He's the master of fast walking.
Remember what Sean said?
- Run slowly. - I must run slowly...
- for the 1st 3km. - Okay.
- To follow his advice? - I'm warming up.
Okay. You're right about that.
My gosh, it's cold. It's freezing today.
(Moorathoner will brave the cold.)
- You got this! - You got this!
- Runners... - You got this!
- Are you runners? - Yes.
How far did you run today?
We're going to run 7km now.
Only 7km? I'm going to run 8km.
- Let's go! - Let's go!
(He's off to an energetic start...)
(thanks to the energy of his fellow runners.)
All right. Let's make the puppy's nose.
- One, two, three, four. - People in the back are calling.
They're reporting about a crazy man.
One, two, three, four.
He told me to run slowly.
(Just like his teacher advised him...)
It's doable so far.
(Easily keeping his pace)
I ran for five minutes.
Not here. I must go a little farther.
Then I can run a full circle there. That will give me a nose.
(Grabbing)
- Hello. I thought I knew him. - Wait.
- Who is that? - No. Hold on. Look.
- It's Bong Tae Gyu! - What?
- What? - That's Bong Tae Gyu.
What's Bong Tae Gyu doing there?
- He lives in Seongbuk-dong. - What?
My gosh. Hello.
- What? - I thought I knew him.
- You treated him like a stranger. - My gosh.
You ran past him and said, "I thought I knew him."
- I... - I just found out.
You didn't recognize him?
- People often hit me like that. - But...
- But... - I know what you mean.
- You do, right? - I know what you mean.
- You could've recognized him. - I didn't.
He has such a distinctive face.
He was self-absorbed then.
- Right. I was. - He couldn't see anyone else. Yes.
I feel so bad. I should text him today.
(Immersed in running, he fails to recognize his friend.)
All right.
I drew the bottom of the nose.
I guess he has to turn like that.
I memorized that I must turn around the buckwheat restaurant.
After starting at the jaw, I must turn a small corner.
That's the nose part.
I need the black nose to complete the puppy.
- I see. You're turning like that. - That's... Yes.
(For the round nose, he must run a block.)
I had to run a block here.
Passing the Korean restaurant...
You must know the area to be able to run there.
That's why I watched the video over ten times.
- Really? - I see.
You'd get the wrong shape if you get confused.
- Right. - Right.
All right. I just drew the nose.
That's fascinating.
I can do this.
There are specific spots.
Here are the parts I'm paying special attention to.
The nose, the ear,
- and the tail. - The tail.
- If I mess up any of them, - Right.
It would ruin the whole drawing.
GPS running is similar to Moosquiat drawing art.
That's the main part I'm focusing on.
I already ran 1km.
- You ran pretty far. - I finished 1km quite fast.
Let's go and draw the head.
(Jogging at ease)
This part was difficult.
This is it.
The stonewall by Gyeongbokgung.
(The stonewall path by Gyeongbokgung)
Is it slightly hilly?
It's not hilly. The path is plain.
I just have to run along the wall.
Seeing restaurants would boost your energy.
I need to smell some food.
(He draws the puppy head by running along the stonewall.)
I knew it.
It's getting hard right about now.
(Panting)
Why does this puppy have such a big head?
(He must run around a bigger block for the head compared to the nose.)
Honestly, I'm a bit surprised.
I watched you run closely.
Your posture is surprisingly better than I expected.
- Really? - I see. Is his posture good?
It's not bad.
(My posture?)
- Really? - Yes.
When people aren't taught properly,
their heels touch first while running.
But your midfoot touches the ground first.
(Hyun Moo can already land on his midfoot first.)
Usually, their upper body shake like this.
- But your upper body is fixed. - You're right.
It's harder to fix your upper body while running.
Your posture is quite good.
- It's good? - I was surprised.
I was born to be a runner.
Hello.
So many people are running there.
My fellow runners.
Runners just get each other. You know?
You only get this feeling after a good sweat.
Don't talk. Just run.
(You must be tired.)
My gosh, it's the Blue House.
I'm running around the Blue House and around the wall...
by Gyeongbokgung Palace.
I went around the Blue House.
(As he goes around the Blue House, )
(he makes out the top of the head.)
I'm seeing everything I saw in the video.
(He runs and runs as he studied in advance.)
Yes, I know this neighborhood. It's Samcheong-dong.
Samcheong-dong.
- It's a nice neighborhood. - Samcheong-dong is nice.
(It's where he'll draw the ear of the puppy.)
The ear is important.
Sujebi.
- It's famous. - That restaurant is delicious.
(That restaurant is delicious!)
There isn't a line today.
(Sniffing)
I could smell it.
(He keeps running as he smells the air.)
Will you pass by the restaurant?
Where am I? Am I going the right way?
What?
I'm lost.
- He's lost. - Oh, no.
The ear needs to come out nicely.
(Worried)
Where am I?
I don't want to stop.
(He checks the map as he walks.)
After passing Churro 101,
I need to cross the road in front of KFCC.
(The turning point for the puppy ear is a bank.)
I need to find KFCC.
(He needs to find a bank.)
KFCC.
(He keeps going straight in search of a turning point.)
Where's KFCC?
- Oh, no. - I was going insane...
because I couldn't see it.
(Moorathoner's expression turns serious.)
Hello.
Sir, do you know where KFCC is?
- KFCC? - Yes. Did I pass it?
- Oh, no. - Did I pass it?
- It's over there. - You should go there again.
- Do you see that over there? - Yes.
If you travel that distance once more, it'll be on your right.
Thank you.
The ear... I ruined it. For goodness' sake.
How annoying!
(Wellness!)
I got distracted by that sujebi place...
and missed KFCC.
For goodness' sake. That sujebi place.
(The sujebi place that distracted Moorathoner is back.)
- That restaurant is tasty. - It's tasty.
KFCC was here.
It was right next to the sujebi place.
I missed it because of the sujebi place.
I should've turned around here. For goodness' sake.
(I missed it because of the sujebi place.)
I'm so upset.
Just how much more did I run?
(Just how much more did I run?)
- The ear. - It became long.
- No. Let's say it's a dobermann. - That's right.
- Let's say it's a dobermann. - That's right.
- It became a rabbit. - It looks cute.
I practically made a deer antler.
I got distracted by sujebi.
I never had that sujebi without waiting in a line.
But there was no line. It got me excited.
"Should I have a bowl?"
"It'd be a win since there's no line."
I got distracted then.
I should've turned there to make a pretty ear,
- but I kept going. - He made a lightning rod.
I went up about 1km.
I was so annoyed.
I felt so victimized. I had wasted my energy.
It was emotionally difficult.
I lost a lot of my spirit then.
(Oh, no)
- Right. - I'm so upset.
- How many kilometers have you run? - I'm so upset.
About 3km, I think.
That means you surpassed your personal record.
- That's right. - That's right.
I surpassed my personal record.
(Moorathoner makes a personal record of 3km)
What's... Is that right?
- Hello. - Hello.
- I'm a fan! - Okay.
- I ran all the way here. - I mean...
- Take this. - Where is it from?
- I'm checking out Seoul. Okay. - It's from my bakery.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Is it okay to eat as I run?
- Is it a toast? - It's pulppang.
- It looks delicious. - It's pulppang that contains...
- the high-quality red bean filling. - It looks delicious.
(Humming in approval)
It's good.
Even marathoners eat simple snacks as they run.
- Exactly. - It's so tasty.
Hold on. Hyun Moo, hold on. Why...
Sean said that I could walk.
After warming up for 3km...
and running for 5km, you can stop if you're exhausted.
I was exhausted.
- You got exhausted early on. - Yes.
- It can't be helped. - You renewed a personal record.
I renewed a personal record.
(As he walks, he celebrates renewing a personal record.)
He looks so weird.
Is it tasty?
Hello.
(He stops to regain energy.)
What's this?
It's so tasty.
(Humming in approval)
This isn't a running video.
Not at all.
Okay.
(His energy is replenished. Okay, let's resume running.)
- Hello. - Hello.
- You're handsome. - Thank you.
All right.
Hello, I'm a runner.
- Is he seriously running there? - I'm a runner.
Please root for me.
- I can't believe it. - He has so much confidence.
- That's courage. - Yes.
What's this?
There are so many fun places.
(He moves forward as people cheer him on.)
It's a pretty street.
(He moves forward along the pretty street.)
- It's a wedding photo shoot. - Congratulations.
- Congratulations on your wedding. - Let's take a photo together!
Congratulations on your wedding.
I can't get married,
but please live happily in my stead!
(Please live happily in my stead!)
I'm cool about it, right?
(I'm cool about it, right?)
- To the citizens... - Hyun Moo must feel lonely...
when he goes home like that.
- No, I didn't even feel lonely... - Really?
Because my body ached so much.
(Thank goodness.)
(Moomoo run is hard on the body, but fills the mind with joy.)
This place is so pretty.
(This place is so pretty.)
What's this place?
It looks fun.
(The scenery of Seoul...)
I didn't know there was such a place in Seoul.
(catches his eyes.)
It's fun to run. There's so much to see.
I had no idea since I only traveled in a car.
That's right.
That's why I run and cycle.
It has been a while since I visited Insa-dong.
- Insadong. - You went to Insa-dong.
If I keep going this way and make a U-turn, it'll be the tail.
You ran a lot.
(Changdeokgung Palace, Donhwamun Gate)
(Since he's near the destination, )
(Moorathoner cheers up with a smile on his face.)
The tail.
(He makes a U-turn after reaching the end of the tail.)
(Smiling)
(He completed the tail.)
The tail.
(He heads to Jongno 3-ga without stopping.)
You're running diligently.
I tried not to walk.
"Even if I take a break, I won't walk."
Hello.
It was a good choice.
Had you run at a place where people weren't around,
- you would've given up. - I can't do that.
I really can't do that.
Let's go all the way to Jongno 3-ga.
All the way there.
The butt and hind leg.
(The puppy's butt and hind leg)
Spicy stir-fried meat sounds good.
Salt bread. Vegan bread.
Bread.
Aged pork rind.
You're going around like someone who has just learned to read Korean.
Seeing so many good restaurants made me happy.
Is Dansungsa still around?
I watched "Saving Private Ryan" there.
- That was a long time ago. - Dansungsa.
First Wholesale Jewelry.
I bought the couple's rings there back in university.
- Oh, my. - Is it still there?
Things stay the same at Jongno 3-ga.
Thanks to the run, I traveled back in time.
I got to revisit the places I frequented back in university...
after a long time when I ran.
I became a university student when I ran.
What?
How do you look older back then?
There was the same jewelry store.
The neighborhood smelled the same.
Running around Seoul was so much fun.
(He runs as he reminisces about the past.)
Jongno 3-ga.
(He arrives at Jongno 3-ga.)
(Jognno 3-ga, the current location)
- How many kilometers have you run? - About 5km.
Just 5km?
(Halting)
- It looks tasty. - How will you pass by those stalls?
- What kinds of takoyaki are there? - Yes?
The spicy flavor...
(We knew it.)
I knew he'd do that.
- The smell was irresistible. - Of course. Those who can resist...
- aren't human. - You shouldn't keep them close.
- How many do you want? - Nine.
- Nine? - What?
- Nine? - That was the smallest size.
- Take a toothpick. - Thank you. Okay.
I couldn't resist the smell.
I'm dying.
- You sat down to eat. - I'm hungry.
If you eat all nine, your stomach will stick out.
Would you like some?
(Sure.)
I hope we aren't stealing all of your food.
It's okay. You can eat all of them.
(They eat one each amicably.)
- It's tasty. - It's tasty, right?
It's even tastier since we stole someone's food.
- Take one more. It's garlic cheese. - One more.
There are big pieces of octopus.
(We can't resist the garlic cheese flavor.)
It's tasty, right?
- I thought you were big, - Okay.
But you're very big.
It's because I run regularly. I run all the time.
- You're cool. - Am I cool?
You ran for the first time today.
(Unbelievable)
Seriously, it's Ripley syndrome.
Have a nice day.
(Sucking)
(He drinks water after eating.)
I was thirsty.
Let's go. I have a long way to go.
That woke me up. That made my eyes open up.
I want this one instead. Peanut.
- This one? - Yes.
- What? - I hope you sell a lot.
- What? - Good luck.
(He buys peanut snacks right away.)
(Humming in approval)
That's the essence of the Moomoo run.
It's a fun run.
I expand horizons.
No one has thought of it before.
You feel Seoul in a fun way.
You're so shameless.
The record and distance don't matter to me.
I ran today. Period.
It's good.
I think I'll be a promoter of running.
Isn't this kind of running nice?
It isn't exhausting. You can take a break.
It's the Moomoo run.
Moomoo's fun run.
(He savors the peanut snacks in a fun manner.)
What will we do with those ears? His ears are about to fall off.
My ears are rotting.
His ears turned dark.
Maybe they'll fall off when he reaches the 8km mark.
It's the day his ears fall off.
- He'll need to get new ears. - The day his ears fall off.
- It's the day his ears fall off. - Yes!
- I'll be like a baby. - It's the day his ears fall off.
(The newborn runner runs bravely.)
He's a newborn runner.
That looks delicious.
(Eating)
Hello.
(Hello.)
(Would you like one?)
How cute!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Bye. - Bye.
Bye.
- She winked. - How cute.
(He arrives at Cheonggyecheon.)
Cheonggyecheon brings back memories.
(With the citizens' resting area as the background)
He's running along Cheonggyecheon.
He's making a big circle.
(Moorathoner cheers up once more.)
(Burping)
I ate too much.
You shouldn't eat even if you're hungry.
That goes without saying.
My throat feels dry.
You ate all the food items that made your throat dry.
Seriously.
They sell an Americano for 3.50 dollars. Okay.
It's on the Blue Ribbon Survey.
- What's this? - Hello.
One iced Americano, please.
I saw a coffee place with the Blue Ribbon Survey plaques.
Thankfully, I found it because I walked.
I mean, I ran.
What? He said it himself.
He got confused too.
- It was a mistake. - You came to your senses briefly.
No.
Then the Ripley syndrome kicked in again.
He isn't all that bad.
Thankfully, I found it because I walked.
I mean, I ran.
I could see it because I ran.
I found a coffee place with the Blue Ribbon Survey plaques.
How else would I have found it?
There was a coffee master.
It's in Seoul,
but I could've lived my entire life without visiting it.
There are things you see when your two feet are on the ground.
His way with words makes him more annoying.
- Would you give me an autograph? - Okay.
Runner.
It's my first autograph as a runner.
(He's absolutely ridiculous.)
Bye.
(Runner Moomoo gets ready before he begins running again.)
(Pouring)
(He pours coffee into his favorite water container.)
Why don't you carry cup noodles as well?
- Fish cake soup on one side... - That's right.
And Americano on the other side.
(That's a good idea.)
(He stores coffee in his chest pocket.)
(He cleans up after himself in a fun manner.)
(Let's cheer up and run now.)
At that moment,
I felt like blood was circulating from the end of my toes...
to the top of my head.
It made me think, "This is the charm of running."
Wasn't it because you drank coffee?
That's right.
It has diuretic properties.
Nicotine coursed through his veins.
- It's caffeine, not nicotine. - Caffeine.
- Hey, come to your senses. - What are you saying?
- It's caffeine, not nicotine. - Nicotine.
- Everyone here is crazy. - Nicotine doesn't have...
diuretic properties.
I'm so embarrassed.
Everyone is having fun, right? This is a fun run.
It's fun indeed.
(After improving his circulation with caffeine, )
(Moorathoner takes a big breath.)
Let's go.
(He runs forward to complete the run.)
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Jonggak Station is quite big.
If it's Exit Ten...
He's so annoying.
It's Bosingak.
They'll ring the bell in two months.
- They'll ring it in two months. - Time passes so quickly.
- I hate it. - They'll ring it in two months.
- It drives me crazy. - They'll ring it in two months.
They always ring the bell for the New Year.
(He passes by Bosingak, )
(a place where the New Year wishes will ring out.)
(About 2km remains.)
He's nearly done.
He looks a bit exhausted now.
(Despite the exhaustion, Moorathoner doesn't give up.)
I keep smelling delicious food.
I can't believe I'm back here.
I'm nearly there.
(He's no longer swayed by temptations.)
Woldae. I'm nearly there.
I completed the puppy.
(Gwanghwamun)
Let's go. I can do it.
(He moves forward as he gasps for breath.)
- Let's go. I can do it. - He worked hard. He didn't stop.
(March forward!)
I have about 1km left.
Victory! Thank you for your hard work.
Yes.
- Hello. - Hello.
(He gives the last spurt thanks to the citizens' support.)
- What is it? - The traffic lights stopped me.
I see. The traffic lights.
(He stops right in front of Woldae, the destination.)
- That's the hardship of a city run. - That's right. It can't be helped.
Runners run on the spot during the wait.
- That's right. They do this. - Yes.
He isn't running there.
Of course not.
(I'm nearly there.)
- You're so cool. - It's nice to meet you.
I'm Honey J's mom.
- Who? - I'm Honey J's mom.
Honey J's mom?
(He runs into Honey J's mom by chance.)
- You ran into everyone... - Are you serious?
- you knew. - It's a real situation.
What?
- Where's Honey J? - Honey J has a performance here.
Does Honey J have a performance here?
Where is she? I should say hello.
- She's inside the building. - Is she inside the building? Gosh.
You're here to see your daughter.
You're much skinnier than you look on TV.
It's because I run.
Running makes me lose weight.
- Did you watch her perform? - I'm going to do that now.
See you later.
I'll get back to running.
(He rushes toward the last point.)
I ran fast so that she'd see me.
It was nice to see Honey J's mom again.
(He's back to Woldae of Gwanghwamun.)
I finished the head.
(He finished the run successfully.)
You did it.
- I did it. - That's incredible.
Hello.
Gosh, that hurts.
Are you a runner? What? Tae Jin!
- What? - What are you doing here? Ouch.
What is Tae Jin doing there?
- What? - Hello.
- Tae Jin was there. - What is Tae Jin doing there?
You met all the celebrities.
- I ran 8km. - Did you run 8km?
Had he run fast and gone home, he wouldn't have met anyone.
- But he was outside all day long. - You're right.
He walked around Seoul endlessly.
- Many people frequent that place. - So many people.
I ran into Bong Tae Gyu...
and Honey J's mom.
- Watch your knees. - Okay. I'll do that.
- Bye. - See you later. Good luck.
Okay.
(It's finally over.)
- You know, the sky turned dark. - I'm back.
How much time did it take?
- He's looking at the result. - The end.
The result.
- Here it is. - Okay.
- Here it is. - The GPS completes it.
It's coming out.
What is it?
(Oh, my!)
It's cute.
(My goodness)
It's coming out.
(The GPS drew the route he ran today.)
What is it?
It's cute.
(My goodness)
It's coming out.
- It's cute. - Isn't it fascinating?
It's so cute.
- You did it. - It's cute.
It's so fascinating.
- It's so cute. - Isn't it really fascinating?
It's so rewarding.
- It's cute. - It isn't an ear, but a leash.
I gave it a leash.
Its tail is so cute. It's like a pig tail.
It's cute.
I should've given it a longer tail.
I ran 11.04km.
- You ran 3km more. - As for the pace...
As for the pace...
That's right.
(Kian84 and Sean running pace was 1km in 5 to 6 minutes.)
As for the pace, 12...
- Twelve? - What does it mean?
Did I run 1km in 12 minutes?
- Twelve minutes? - Twelve minutes?
(Sighing)
- Did I run 1km in 12 minutes? - That rivals the speed of my gecko.
Hyun Moo, I can run 1km in 8 minutes at the very least.
- That's fast. - That's slower than walking.
(1km in 12 minutes)
MINHO, what's your record for 1km?
It's 4 minutes and 30 seconds or 5 minutes.
- It's 4 minutes and 30 seconds. - It's 4 minutes and 30 seconds.
- That's a stressful run. - That's incredible.
- I can't do that. - But it's fun to break your record.
That's right.
You should try finishing under 12 minutes next time.
It was 12 minutes and 55 seconds.
How does 12 minutes and 30 seconds sound?
- Is that a bit too hard? - Hold on.
If I bring it down by 30 seconds each time,
I'll always be happy.
You can break a new record each time.
Right. That sounds fun.
That was why he took it.
I should post it as a portrait photo.
Gwanghwamun will be slightly seen.
It's a way to make people curious.
"Where could this be?"
(He takes the photo after checking the composition.)
(Looking away)
Gosh, that was great.
I should post it right away.
The song will be "JUMP."
(He chooses the song and posts it in a flash.)
Done.
My first run.
Don't feel embarrassed.
He got one like as he posted it and liked his own post.
BLACKPINK's song?
(I'm filling up with self-love.)
You feel a sense of accomplishment...
after completing a challenge.
It has been a while since I have felt that.
I barely had any challenges these days.
(He felt a burst of excitement...)
(as it had been a while for him to make a challenge.)
I felt proud of myself for setting myself a mission...
and being able to accomplish it.
(He didn't stop moving even during his struggles.)
Say something.
I don't know what I should say.
I feel bad for having John Lennon's song playing to this.
I was always called an oldie,
Fathermoo,
and a 600-year-old.
Still, the eldest made it happen.
I give it to you that you completed the course.
I want to compliment Moomoo for putting it into action...
without just saying it with words.
I love you.
(I love myself.)
(Running is a Mental Battle)
Gosh, it's so cold!
A mental battle?
- My gosh! - Gosh, what's going on?
- Gosh! - Did he pass away?
- How can you say that? - Hold on.
- He's definitely here. - You're so mean.
I will start with the cleansing.
All of my runs end with a massage.
Running can end up making my skin rot.
That will be terrible for me.
I can't stand my skin rotting.
I'm Moorincess, after all.
So that's what's going on?
My skin has to be lifted up by hand.
Up tight!
The decollete must be massaged along with a detox...
to remove the toxins.
Toxins out.
The sags must be lifted up.
(Choking)
- What was that? - He has risen!
- He has returned! - He has returned!
He has resurrected!
I hear these stories once in a while from foreign news.
- People who have come back to life. - Right.
There would be people who would come back to life after two days.
I fall asleep in five minutes.
(This is a miracle.)
He has returned!
(The feeling of reborn)
(Clearing his throat)
I will say a word to the shy runners.
The biggest problem with shy runners...
is that they are scared to start.
If you enjoy a fun run like this,
you can all become runners.
Come on in to Moomoo's Fun Run World.
Your form was really nice earlier. I got so surprised.
- You ran well. - I'm serious.
I got so surprised.
You're talking about the crosswalk run, right?
- Right. When you sprinted. - "Crosswalk run."
- I got so surprised. - Really?
- He did run well. - Right. I got so surprised.
I'll gather the ones who are distant from running...
and start a Fun Run Crew.
That sounds like a good idea.
Moomoo's Fun Run Crew.
I'll admit it if you manage to run with KEY.
Really? Do you want to join the Fun Run Crew, MINHO?
No.
Come on in to Moomoo's Fun Run World.
(You are invited to the Fun Run World.)
(I Live Alone)
(Ja Yeon's Season)
"Ja Yeon's Season."
(Ja Yeon has brought together many different things.)
There are a bunch of things gathered.
(Rustling)
- What is that? - She has a backpack like that?
(She even brings out a mysterious backpack...)
(early in the morning.)
Why is it so early?
(Good morning.)
That's such a cute cat.
(Piled up)
They're all for secondhand trading.
She'll be selling all of those for a secondhand trade?
Right. Unnecessary things should be sold.
(Mysterious items have been brought out from the storage room.)
- What? - Gosh!
Camping?
It's 6°C.
(If it's 6°C...)
I probably won't need a jacket.
As fall has come,
I'm planning to go on a backpacking trip.
I had friends around me who enjoying backpacking,
so I followed them from time to time.
It's perfect to go out right now.
- It's perfect right now. - Right.
It's my second time going alone.
Isn't that the rice she won last time?
- Right. - Right.
Gosh, it feels nice to see it.
(She puts in the minced garlic into an empty container.)
She must be planning to cook.
She has to make food there.
(She packs just what she needs with the ingredients.)
She must go camping often.
She has all of those containers as well.
I think they're containers for cosmetics. I just used them.
It's most important to cut down on the weight of the backpack.
(Cutting)
(The salt is packed with foil. Liquids are packed into containers.)
How diligent.
She seems like an expert by the way she's packing things.
(She prepares a cooler bag for the ingredients.)
You end up buying everything for a camping trip...
if you don't go regularly.
- I'm a camper who buys everything. - A fake camper.
- I see. - Right.
I lend my friends with things.
This is you when you go camping.
You spend more money than going to a five-star hotel.
- I see. - Gosh.
I've been quite distant from camping these days.
Do you still have that car?
- I sold it. - He sold it.
Hyun Moo is doing a great job with making Korea's economy flow.
(Feeling proud)
(She packs her backpack diligently.)
That backpack can carry so many things.
- Right. - How many liters can it carry?
It can carry 70L.
Did you say 70L?
That's the extra-large one.
(Putting in)
(Struggling)
(It's becoming harder to put things in.)
The light things go in first.
The heavy things are placed closer toward the back as possible.
I try to place the heavy things...
- toward the upper back. - Since the heavy things...
might make you lean back.
It's less harder...
if the heavy things are placed against your back.
- Seoul National University! - Otherwise, you'd fall backward.
I think it's right to place the heavy things on top.
- I guess so. - Right.
(She even uses the sides of the backpack.)
How heavy was that backpack then?
I think it was around 15 to 20kg.
- Just like for an army march. - Right.
Heave-ho!
(Sliding down)
Gosh, I'm already exhausted.
Everyone rests like that during a march.
Right.
- Just like that. - Everyone is like that.
I'm seeing that pose after ten years.
Gosh.
The snack given is eaten just like that.
Right. Everyone sleeps on the concrete floor like that.
That's tough to carry even for men.
With rotational force,
it isn't that hard to carry.
Seoul National University!
(Gosh, rotational force?)
(Getting up)
Is that okay?
It must be heavy.
(She carries the backpack with the scientific principle.)
Let's go.
Gosh, let's go.
(She sets out for her march.)
The weather is great.
(She walks while humming.)
She must not be driving there.
Is there a camping site near her place?
The weather is really nice today.
It feels cool.
I hope the autumn leaves look beautiful.
(Rummaging)
Gosh, the 20th minute.
- What is it? - It will come on the 20th minute.
I purposely chose not to drive today.
It feels like an opportunity to experience more coincidences.
Also, when I get there when I'm all exhausted,
it feels a lot more rewarding.
It's like putting my body to the test.
Right. You need to feel that.
- There's someone who understands. - Definitely.
The campground I will be going to...
needs me to take the Gyeongui-Jungang Line...
and a town bus.
(It takes around two hours.)
The town bus goes around only 3 to 4 times a day.
- It'll be terrible if I miss it. - Gosh.
- What happens if you miss it? - I rushed in the morning...
to take that bus.
I have to wait for four hours if I miss the town bus.
That can't happen.
- You have to hurry then. - I had to be there on time.
The 20th minute.
(In a hurry)
The subway for the Gyeongui-Jungang Line...
- comes every 30 minutes. - Right. They don't come often.
You will miss the town bus if you miss the subway.
(I'll miss the town bus if I miss this subway!)
(Running)
The 20th minute!
It's coming in 4 minutes! There are 3 minutes left!
I don't think you can make it with four minutes left.
Gosh, she's quick.
- Gosh. - Gosh.
(Oksain Bolt gets summoned as she's in a hurry.)
Oksain Bolt.
I couldn't beat her at all.
How can she be beaten when she's training all the time...
on her own like this?
Toward Yangjeong Station.
(Panting)
Okay.
- She made it? - She still made it.
- That's amazing. - I made it.
Why does the view from the subway look so beautiful today?
(Donong Station)
(She takes the subway for around 40 minutes.)
(Asin Station)
(She arrives at Asin Station.)
- Asin? - Asin.
The air already feels better.
(She quickly shops for groceries.)
Here it is!
(Let's see.)
(Asin-ri, Asin Station Entrance)
- This is the bus stop? - Asin-ri, Asin Station.
(Heave-ho)
(Shall we take a breather?)
(But the bus comes right away.)
It's here.
(I must not miss it.)
(Run, Ja Yeon!)
Hello.
I'm headed to the recreational forest.
Why did you tell the driver where you're going?
Are you showing off?
"You know that that I'm Actress Ok Ja Yeon, right?"
"I'm not Ok Ja Yeon."
No.
The last stop of that bus is the end of town,
but the recreational forest is further up top from the town.
It'll be a one-hour walk from the last stop,
but the driver will take you there if you tell him.
(Amazed)
So the driver won't go up there if you don't tell him.
- That's really nice. - That's the charm...
- of buses in the countryside. - There's that charm.
Since a lot of elders live there,
the drivers take them to where they need to be.
Right. They can even say their addresses.
- Right. - Right.
- That's a good culture. - Right.
- Korean culture. - Yes. Good culture.
It's great as it isn't cold.
It feels so cool.
(She looks out the window...)
(and the friendly scenery can be seen.)
Bus rides are the best in the countryside.
(Looking around)
The view on the other side was better.
I see.
- I do that at times as well. - Right.
(She moved to a seat with a better view.)
(Focused)
The countryside houses look great. There are crocks?
Gosh, there are crocks.
You can't see those things when you are driving.
- You only see what's ahead of you. - Right.
I enjoy taking the bus as well.
(After enjoying the bus vibes for a while, )
(the bus goes up the curvy slope.)
Gosh, it's going really high up.
You almost walked for an hour if you didn't know that.
Right.
(Clapping)
(She gets there comfortably thanks to the driver.)
So there's a place like that.
(Recreational Forest)
- This place is very popular. - I see.
It's hard to book a spot.
- This place? - Yes.
- Why? - Everyone dreams of...
- going wild camping, - Right.
- but it's hard to actually do that. - Right.
It's a recreational forest where you can enjoy wild camping vibes.
(A place where you can enjoy wild camping vibes!)
- It's a place full of nature. - Right.
You have to book a spot in advance?
- Yes. - So you can't stay at...
any mountain you wish to stay at, right?
If you were to say, "I'm going to sleep on this mountain..."
That means you're just lost.
(Understanding)
(She arrives at her destination after around two hours.)
It's really far away.
So this is the spot?
- Hello. - Hello.
- Did you make a reservation? - Yes.
- I'm Ok Ja Yeon. - Right.
Right.
You may never make a fire with any firewood.
Firewood isn't allowed, but I can use a stove.
- Right. - You can make simple dishes.
- This is our current location. - Right.
- This is the maintenance office. - Right.
- After around a 600m walk, - Yes?
You can settle down at a camping spot of your choice.
So there's a place like that.
You'll find a much better view toward the oak tree forest.
- Understood. - Right.
- Have a great time. - Thank you.
(Thank you.)
Gosh.
(Full of excitement)
It's 600m away.
(Let's walk up 600m!)
Let's walk up 600m.
(Recreational Forest)
Up the path.
(I just need to walk up the path.)
Gosh, it smells nice.
Cosmos!
They're beautiful!
- They're beautiful! - It's great here.
Cosmos.
(The air and view are great.)
(Walking up)
(Panting)
You're a pretty one.
How pretty.
It's a dandelion.
(Panting)
Why are you so pretty?
How did just one flower pop out?
This is a banana tree.
- Bananas. - Your name says it all.
(Panting)
- You're slowly losing your breath. - Right?
She won't be talking as much now.
- What is that? - Gosh.
- What? - That can't be true.
(Ja Yeon is walking up to find the right spot.)
I still won't be halfway up.
(Panting)
- What is that? - Gosh.
- What? - That can't be true.
(She has a backpack that is as big as her.)
She's literally hiking.
That looks exhausting.
(Surprised)
Gosh, this is tough.
That must've been really tough.
Leaning back just a little bit would make her fall on her back.
I have to go up 600m?
(Panting)
Her breathing sounds a lot rougher.
It's like putting my body to the test.
That's part of the fun of it.
The fun of putting her body to the test.
Gosh, I can't go up!
(It's a very steep slope.)
It's a very steep slope.
That would be exhausting even without a backpack.
- Right. - Right.
It's like doing lunges.
What kind of people are those who go hiking?
- Look at that. - Ask for a ride!
Hitchhike!
(Letting out a breath)
(Panting)
Modern technology is moving by.
(Letting out a breath)
(I will go my way.)
It was very tough.
I felt the weight on my shoulders.
The weight of life.
- Right. - There's such a saying,
"Bearing the weight on one's shoulders."
I learned the true meaning of that.
(Panting)
(Stomach growling)
(I'm hungry and exhausted.)
(There seems to be no end to the slope.)
- What? - Is that the right way?
She has a hip-hop mindset.
(The final course of hardship was waiting for her.)
(Struggling)
That's the wild camping she wanted.
(Impressed)
- Nice. - It's this spot?
It's really nice.
(The oak tree forest unfolds after her suffering.)
- It's nice here. - This was the destination?
There are a lot of acorns.
This is certainly the oak tree forest.
There we go. I should look for a point.
(Feeling refreshed)
(Oak Tree Forest Observatory)
"Oak Tree Forest."
(A place hidden in nature)
It does look really nice.
- It's really nice. - It was great.
(Full of the smell of fall)
- Pine cones. - It's really nice.
Let's look for a point.
Are there no other tents?
It's first come, first served.
Taking the best spot first...
- is the most important. - Right.
- Right. - It's first come, first served?
(Amazed)
(This spot is great.)
- This is it! - It's nice here.
This is an excellent spot.
Gosh.
There should be a nice view.
Which way is this facing?
(Let's take a look.)
Southwest.
(It's a good direction as well.)
- The leaves are changing color. - It feels a bit like "Exhuma."
- It gives off those vibes. - "Exhuma."
She does feel like a guru from behind.
She would have a white beard when she turns around.
Not a woman?
- Yes, it's just how it feels. - The vibe.
She was a natural person.
You know how people wear a ponytail in Cheonghak-dong Village.
- That's right. - A ponytail?
- The original ponytails. - Of course.
They'd have a long beard...
- when they turn around. - That's right.
(They'd have a long beard when they turn around.)
It's so vast.
I look like someone who came to buy a property.
There are some rocks on the ground.
But it's not too bad to sleep here.
(Shall I begin now?)
(Fluttering)
(Now that she's picked a spot, she starts setting up the tent.)
- She's doing it for real. - How does she do that?
(Fascinated)
(Skillfully unfolding the poles...)
(and pitching the tent smoothly)
(She pitches the tent in an instant.)
- She sets it up so fast. - Gosh, are you done already?
Yes, I just need a cover.
That didn't take long.
But... Gosh, she's so good.
She set it up so fast.
Camping must be fun since she's good.
(Hitting)
Gosh, she hammers it with a rock.
(She hammers the stakes with a rock.)
(The 1-person tent is set up in no time.)
- She's really good. - How can she do it so skillfully?
She's really good.
We've only seen people who don't know how to set up a tent.
We finally got to see...
- the real deal. - Someone who does it for real.
We finally have the real deal.
(The real camper keeps busy without resting.)
(Rumbling)
Gosh, I'm hungry.
(It's already 1:30pm. Her stomach is growling like thunder.)
- She must be hungry. - You should eat something fast.
Your stomach is making animal noises.
It's roaring.
I'm starving.
(Let's set it up quickly.)
Yes, let's eat first.
(She sets up a camping chair in no time.)
(Pulling)
All of them must be light.
- They are. - They're really small.
(Setting up smoothly)
That's really small and cute.
(Opening...)
(and opening again)
(If you fix the back...)
- A stove... - They're so cute.
Oh, that's a pot stand?
There are so many things in her backpack.
I have everything in there. I have a house and a kitchen too.
Exactly. That's so...
That's totally science.
(How much the backpack can hold is scientific.)
I'm so hungry.
(She washes her hands clean.)
What is that?
Are they beans?
- Beans? - Red beans?
Yes, they're red beans.
Why did you put in red beans?
(Pouring water into the pot with red beans)
(She smoothly sets up the stove.)
That can be used in the mountains, right?
The lunch menu is the dish of my dream for camping.
It's red bean kalguksu.
- Goodness. - Why make red bean kalguksu...
in the mountains?
Red bean kalguksu?
- You soaked the beans in advance. - Yes, I did the day before.
- That takes a lot of work. - What about the noodles?
- I should roll out the dough. - What?
You're rolling out the dough there?
Did you open a restaurant there?
Is that even possible?
Normally, people bring food...
- that's easy to make. - That's right.
- Like ones you can just boil. - Like budae jjigae.
- Or something you can just grill. - That's right.
But going camping made me want to try new things.
Various menus.
(That's how she challenged herself into making red bean kalguksu.)
That looks fun, though.
As for noodles, I'm using whole wheat flour.
The goal is to make red bean kalguksu of my own.
- Just like making acorn jelly. - Right, she made acorn jelly too.
- She's good with food like that. - That's right.
You have mastered traditional dishes.
- She's like a master. - A master, yes.
(As a master, she prepares a healthy meal.)
She eats healthy food even while camping.
You brought the bag to make it easy.
Yes, right in that bag.
(Kneading)
(She can't give up the homemade touch even while camping.)
It looks like a food journey.
This is fun.
(Ok Ja Yeon's Traditional Food Journey)
(Kneading gently with the touch of a master)
Oh, she's using the bottle as a roller.
That's the fun of it.
Humans use tools.
She rolled it pretty well.
(Rolling the dough for a while)
It felt really good. The dough rolled really well.
I cut the dough, and it was really smooth.
I felt like the noodles would turn out well. I was really excited.
Doing that...
in nature felt out of place, and it was so much fun.
It felt like the tall trees were watching me.
It felt like the birds were watching too.
It was like I was having fun playing house.
I get what it feels like.
It's like "Little Forest."
The noodles turned out well.
- It's in such good quality. - Yes.
- Not bad, right? - It turned out well.
(After making whole wheat noodles...)
(Thinking)
What?
Are you making chopsticks out of that?
That's right.
It's my second dream.
In YouTube videos,
they make chopsticks out of wood...
that fell off.
(It's called wood carving.)
I thought of giving it a try,
so I bought a carving knife.
And so, I brought it today with ambition.
The ones who are good at that are amazing.
They even make bowls too.
She's like Geppetto.
Or Okppetto.
Okppetto?
(Scraping)
(Carving)
(Master Okppetto only carves wood without speaking.)
It took really long.
Even though it was a thin piece of wood...
It's too short.
(She kept on carving for a while.)
That's the fun of it.
- There's nothing else to do either. - Right.
My right arm will be thicker.
They've become really thin.
- She should open a studio. - You can even take them home.
- That's usable. - You should take them home.
They've become really thin.
(Washing her hands as she touched wood)
Oh, I can crush them now.
It's crushable now.
- They turned out totally nice. - That looks good.
(Putting it in another container)
(Then she adds water to make a red bean porridge.)
- That's why she brought salt. - The one she packed separately.
Sweet and salty.
She's making all that...
- with those small tools. - Exactly.
(Adding whole wheat noodles into the water...)
(that boiled red beans)
So she's cooking the noodles first.
She's amazing.
(Stirring with the chopsticks she just made)
Look at the chopsticks.
- She did a good job. - It's wood carving.
They all break easily.
Goodness.
You should've kneaded it more.
Darn it.
(Oh, no...)
They all broke off the moment I touched them.
They're too short.
(Let's add them and boil first.)
This isn't kalguksu.
But it looks pretty good.
It'd have been amazing if she had kimchi.
- That'd be perfect. - It looks good, though.
I know because I make pasta.
You should've added eggs.
Whole wheat noodles break more easily.
It was my first time making noodles.
You can think of it as...
- whole wheat sujebi. - Of course.
- You cut them as you eat anyway. - Of course.
- As long as it's delicious. - Yes, of course.
She didn't get to use the chopsticks in the end.
You're right.
- I couldn't use the chopsticks. - She couldn't.
- It's all right. - I had to use a spoon to scoop it.
It's 3:47pm.
It took you 3 hours. You started at 1pm when you got there.
(Her lunch is ready after a long journey of three hours.)
(Blowing)
(A deeply moving first bite)
That kalguksu must cost a lot.
She should get 100 dollars for it.
How did it taste?
Gosh, anything must taste good.
She'd enjoy it even if it's not delicious.
I can't say it's delicious.
When you were starving?
- No. - How come?
It's because the whole wheat noodles...
You didn't season it a little?
I should've added salt while making the noodles.
So you didn't add salt.
The noodles didn't mix well.
The noodles weren't good.
- It's hard. - Ja Yeon...
Ja Yeon, the food you make...
isn't that appetizing.
- Didn't you say she was good? - What did you say?
They look like they'd help you lose weight.
- That's not true. - You can't say that...
as someone who made that horrible kimchi fried rice.
I feel like I'm a better cook.
- No! - My gosh.
- This is... - I'm quite good too.
That's because it was my first time making noodles.
You should really reflect on yourself to hear that from Kian84.
- That's... - No.
- It's too... - He's not even listening.
It's leaning to healthy food too much.
- You gave up on the taste. - But it's good...
- She sounds really upset. - It took me three hours.
I've never seen her get this worked up.
I'm sweating.
That's not true.
Have a cooking competition with him with a time limit.
- You should. - Let them compete,
- and we can have a blind test. - I'd make noodles again.
- Wait. You're going to eat it? - What?
- You're going to eat it? - I can just taste it a little.
I'll show you my skills.
I'm just eating it since I made it.
(Consuming it with a heavy responsibility)
Why am I sad?
(Cawing)
- Crows are cawing. - Even they won't eat that.
They're kind of laughing at you.
Why does it feel like they're laughing at me?
(Cawing)
I should make dinner.
You're making dinner right away?
I had to. It was late.
You should have something delicious.
The sun has gone down a lot.
(Rustling)
(Ja Yeon takes something out from the tent.)
Food?
A cutting board?
Since the sun is setting,
it's a little cold.
You have a kitchen, a bed, a house,
- and a closet in that backpack. - And a closet.
(She sits down after putting on a jacket.)
(Putting it down)
Is that a cutting board?
- It looks like it. - A cutting board...
- What is it? - What is it?
Recently, my friend who does plays...
said they pressed flowers because the flowers they received...
withered really fast.
- I see. - Press flowers?
(The flower petals we kept between pages when we were young)
I see.
Didn't you all have one in a frame?
Of course.
I used to do that a lot when I was younger.
I haven't seen that for a long while.
They said if you press just one piece,
you can remember the bouquet.
I thought I should make one too.
Then I came camping,
and I thought making that could help me remember...
the campsites I've been to.
That's why I thought of pressing flowers.
- That's romantic. - That really is romantic.
There weren't any pretty leaves from this tree.
It's an oak grove, but there weren't any pretty oak leaves.
It was an oak grove,
so I wanted to pick a pretty oak leaf on the ground.
But only the insect-eaten ones fell on the ground.
(Putting the leaves together carefully...)
(with the flower pressing kit)
Oh, there's a kit for it?
What's this? How fascinating.
And then...
(Putting a paper and a wooden board on the flowers)
Press it.
I guess you must tighten it with a screw.
It's fascinating.
Oh, like that?
That really is romantic.
Oh, you can press it this hard.
We used to use a paper dictionary...
- to press. - That's right.
That's right.
I wonder how it'll turn out.
Can that be made in a day?
- How long does it take? - I think it needs a few days.
At least three days.
It's been 3 to 4 days.
- You brought it? Gosh. - Oh, my.
You're seeing the result for the first time with us?
- Yes, I don't know either. - Really?
- I don't know if it worked or not. - Oh, my.
Did it turn out okay?
- It must be pretty. - All right.
I'm nervous as I ruined red bean kalguksu as well.
- Don't be nervous. - Let's see.
(All eyes on her)
We're seeing this together for the first time.
(Amazed)
(The pressed flowers Ja Yeon made when she went camping)
- Drumroll. - We're seeing this together...
for the first time.
(Amazed)
- It's pretty. - It turned out really well.
One by one.
(The flowers and leaves were dried beautifully.)
- It looks like it's embroidered. - The flowers are pretty.
- I know. It looks like a brooch. - It's so pretty.
It looks like a pin for your clothes.
The flowers turned out better than I thought.
- They turned out really nicely. - The flowers turned out well.
- The flowers turned out well. - The flowers are pretty.
How pretty.
- The flowers are pretty. - The flowers are pretty.
I think...
it'll be better to laminate it.
Are you really giving them out?
- Yes. - You're giving them to us?
Yes.
- Really? - Yes.
(Smiling)
- Won't they break? - But this...
We should keep it in a book.
- Sounds good. - This one's really pretty.
Let's keep it in the wallet.
- It's so fascinating. - It's pretty.
- It's really fascinating. - This is really pretty.
It smells nice.
(Feeling proud)
We got to see nice things thanks to you.
It's really fascinating.
(Thinking)
It feels like I just finished eating, but...
I need to make dinner before the sun sets.
- Gosh. - You need to move quickly.
(Rustling)
(She takes out a big bag from the backpack.)
What is that?
(Jeju red tilefish)
- Red tilefish? - Red tilefish?
You brought red tilefish?
For dinner,
I'm making red tilefish over rice and Jeju-style red tilefish soup.
- Red tilefish over rice? - Gosh.
Red tilefish?
I told you I went camping on Jeju Island, right?
I bought a huge red tilefish then...
and grilled it.
It was so good.
Since then, I've ordered red tilefish.
I made red tilefish over rice with the one I ordered...
when I went camping last time, and it was really good.
So I thought I should make red tilefish soup as well this time.
Amazingly delicious red tilefish meal.
(Taking out ingredients for the amazingly delicious dinner)
That's why you packed seasoning.
Yes, that's how you should pack. You can't bring new ones every time.
(Heating up the pot first)
(Kelp in rice?)
First, bring the rice and kelp to a full boil.
(Grabbing)
(Focused)
(Cutting it skillfully)
- Is it half-dried? - Yes.
(Spreading the red tilefish that she cut)
- What's that? - It's sesame oil.
- I see. - I see.
(Applying sesame oil thoroughly)
All set.
- Oh, you grill it. - She grills it first.
- Gosh. - You're amazing.
That looks delicious.
(Golden brown)
That looks good.
(I hope it grills well.)
(Grabbing a handful of scallions while the red tilefish is grilled)
(Cutting it into an edible size)
(Checking)
When the water boils down,
lower it to medium heat.
Add scallions to the rice.
Oh, to the rice?
(Spreading scallions on the rice)
You can't give up on scallions.
(Adding the well-grilled red tilefish on top)
- My gosh. - That looks really good.
Let it steam for a while and have it.
Red tilefish over rice is really good.
It must be so good.
(Red tilefish with bones is put into the kettle.)
- Side without bones is for rice. - That's right.
- Side with bones is for soup. - Soup.
- It's perfect. - Gosh.
(Cutting the radish and chillies she brought into a bite size)
(Adding everything into the kettle)
(Seasoning it with minced garlic and soy sauce she brought)
That's a good idea.
- Boiling everything in a kettle. - Yes.
(She prepared dinner smoothly unlike lunch.)
(Spreading a mat on the side in nature)
(All of a sudden?)
Goodness.
(Lying on the mat where she can keep her eye on the pot)
I hope it becomes delicious.
There's madness in her eyes.
(True madness)
(Staring at it intently while casting a spell)
What were you thinking then?
Because my lunch was ruined,
I couldn't take my eyes off dinner.
(Super focused without even moving)
(Rushing to the pot while keeping an eye on it)
(Grabbing)
(She sits down with a cup.)
(A green bottle from the backpack?)
- Goodness. - For real?
You're having soju.
(Suddenly, her hands move fast.)
You're drinking as is?
- It's really good. - But you don't drink.
- She was under a lot of stress. - No.
I can drink a little. That's Chungha.
I can drink that much.
(Happy)
- She looks the happiest now. - I know.
Happiness.
(Careful)
(The red tilefish soup is being cooked well.)
All set.
(It's all set.)
(Taking out the well-cooked red tilefish carefully)
- Look how the meat comes apart. - That must be really good.
What a luxury.
(Getting lots of radish as well)
It's like beef bone soup.
I can't wait to see the rice.
The rice.
(The red tilefish over rice is cooked well.)
- Is this real? - It turned out so well!
- It looks so good. - What is this?
I added just the right amount of water.
- It's not an AI-generated image? - No.
AI generates images really well these days.
(Putting on a hat first as it's cold)
(Putting the pot that cooled down in her lap)
(Amazed)
Gosh, the smell.
(Satisfied)
The rice turned out so well with scorched rice too.
It looks so good.
(Taking a bite of the rice she mixed well)
It was amazingly successful.
- Amazingly successful? - It was a success.
It's sweet.
(Adding the deep red tilefish soup to the rice)
(Enjoying a bite of rice)
(And enjoying a bite of nature with eyes)
It's too good to have it by myself.
I love pot rice.
It must've been really delicious.
All the struggles I had while climbing up disappeared.
Having fish in the mountains isn't so bad.
- Yes. - It's really nice.
The soup got even thicker.
(Surprised)
It's really good if you eat it when the sun sets.
- Because it's at night. - You go camping to enjoy that.
(Staring)
(Quietly gazing at nature)
I don't know why,
but the struggles I bring for myself...
makes me feel good.
I don't know the reason.
Whether it's meaningful or not,
when I need to feel the sense of accomplishment...
after doing what I wanted to do,
I do such things.
Actually, it's not important to make red bean kalguksu.
(Actually, it's not important to make red bean kalguksu.)
What's the point of walking up the path...
that can easily be traveled with a car?
My point exactly.
It's meaningless.
But I wanted to immerse myself into something meaningless...
that doesn't necessarily give any outcome.
Being satisfied with it by myself without anyone knowing.
That makes me feel good.
- That's so nice. - I think it's really nice.
I can relate to her.
It's so pretty.
(Although I had it hard today, )
(I am very happy now.)
(This is so nice.)
One might think it's hot chocolate. It's Chungha.
(No Matter What Anyone Says, I Love What Makes Me Happy)
(Next story)
(After a decade of dominating the Premier League, )
(his transfer to Korea shook the world.)
(I hope to see Jesse Lingard on I Live Alone soon.)
(The current captain of FC Seoul)
Hello.
(Soccer player, Jesse Lingard)
(It's been 2 years since he started living alone in Korea.)
(With a hair cap, )
(he stretches.)
(Lingard's apartment with a Han River view)
(Filled with hipster vibe)
(Flopping down)
(Did you sleep well?)
(A morning greeting with Wilson)
(I'll dress you up, Wilson.)
(Just a little bit...)
(Wilson with Lingard's little touch-up)
(He talks with someone on the phone soon after.)
(It's his only daughter, Hope.)
(The dad who lives abroad is happy to see his daughter on a screen.)
(Just a little bit...)
(Ironing his clothes little by little)
(It's a little cold.)
(He walked a little bit more...)
(and reached Seongsu-dong.)
(Jesse!)
(Hello.)
(Greeting the passersby joyfully)
(Grabbing a basket)
(He went into a cosmetics store naturally.)
(Give me one, please.)
(Is it nice? Then I'll get two.)
(Twice as happy)
(Doing skincare as soon as he comes home)
(Two if it's nice)
(Bringing in a mysterious bag from outside)
(I'm really hungry.)
(It's more delicious if you get a taste of everything.)
(I Am Getting Used to the Life in Korea)
(I Am Getting Used to the Life in Korea a Little)
(On the wide expanse of sand, )
(someone is riding a horse energetically.)
(It's Bacterrius...)
(on a white horse?)
(Nice)
(Woo Il is here.)
(Introducing my hobby)
(I came for horse riding in fall.)
(Forget Bacterrius.)
(The real Terrius' dash)
Two. Good.
(Good job.)
(Patting)
(Spitting out)
(Why would you spit it out?)
(I have a lot more to learn about horse riding.)
(Even his legs are shaking.)
(It's not easy to become Terrius.)
- No, look. - Where are you going?
(Someone who consoles Bacterrius is...)
(his close friend, Yun Hwa?)
- Oh, hello. - Hello.
(Where Bacterrius and Yun Hwa headed to...)
(is a market with generous vendors.)
(This is exciting.)
(Woo Il!)
(He's super popular too.)
Hey, Auntie!
(Maybe I am Market Terrius?)
(How many are you going to buy?)
(It'll be on me, Terrius.)
(Market Terrius' wallet is opening.)
(Are you happy that I'm rich?)
(Yes!)
(I'll get everything for you.)
(Woo Il bought this.)
A man like me...
(Today, I'm the Real Terrius)